rockpals.com 2018-08-17

# Privacy Policy - Support - Rockpals

Rockpals,respects your privacy and the purpose for which our website visitors provide us information. We do not share, sell, or rent any of the information collected to any third parties and do not intend to do so in the future.

* * *

####  **Information Collected** **：**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order or subscribe to our newsletter.

When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address.You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

####  Information Collected by Others:

This notice addresses only the policy of Rockpals' website and not sites that users access via links from our site. Orlando Products, Inc. is not responsible for the information collection policies of other sites, nor for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our website, nor for the information or content contained therein. Often links to other websites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to our visitors. Users are advised to review the privacy policy of other websites.

* * *

####  About cookies:

Rockpals does not use cookies.

* * *

#### 

Third Party Links:

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. 

Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

* * *

#### 

#### 

#### 

Online Privacy Policy Only:

#### 

#### 

This online Privacy Policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to any information collected offline.

* * *

#### 

####  Updating, Correcting, and Deleting Personal Information:

If you would like to have your personal information removed from our records, please send an e-mail with "Remove personal information" in the subject line.

* * *

####  Periodic Policy Changes:

Please note that Rockpals reviews its privacy practices from time-to-time (i.e. to track technology and/or legal changes), and that these practices are subject to change. To ensure continuing familiarity with the most current version of our privacy policy, please bookmark and periodically review this page.  
This policy statement is made in the name of Rockpals. and is effective as of December  11, 2017. This statement does not create an agreement between Rockpals and users, and as such, does not create any legal rights for any party.

* * *

####  Contact Us:

By using our site, you consent to our website Privacy Policy. If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, please contact us at [mt@rockpals.com](mailto:support@rockpals.com).
